<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://chongniki.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 16:34:37 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://chongniki.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://chongniki.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 16:34:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chongniki.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello, I&amp;rsquo;m Niki. I am a final year student at Coventry University, studying towards a degree in Information Technology. Through my endeavours, I have discovered my passion - Data. This site is dedicated to displaying my projects, and ventures.
Over the years, I have created a considerable presence online, on mediums such as Github, LinkedIn, Twitter, Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diving into NLP with Topic Modelling</title>
      <link>https://chongniki.github.io/posts/topic_modelling_project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 16:32:25 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chongniki.github.io/posts/topic_modelling_project/</guid>
      <description>Over the summer of 2017, I was fortunate enough to land a Data Science internship at the Center of Applied Data Science (Malaysia). My colleagues were incredibly patient and supportive throughout my time there.
During my time there, I was introduced to Natural Language Processing, where textual data could be machine readable, and understandable. This was mind-blowing! Language, one of the attributes that make human, human - could be understood by machines; This thought astounded me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fitbit Analysis</title>
      <link>https://chongniki.github.io/posts/fitbit_project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 16:32:25 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chongniki.github.io/posts/fitbit_project/</guid>
      <description>I recently got a fitbit, and have been using it for the past 2 months or so. Curious, I decided to download my fitbit data to explore with. I am an avid believer in learning by doing - which is why I decided to practice my data cleaning and analysis skills with my own fitbit data. With the data, preprocessed the data using pandas and numpy, and plotted it with matplotlib.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://chongniki.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 16:32:25 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chongniki.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>Fitbit Analysis Will I take a nap today? An analysis of my Fitbit data.
Topic Modelling of Tweets What are the topics have I been talking about the most? My first NLP attempt.
Web Scraping with Selenium Crawling the web for data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>find me on</title>
      <link>https://chongniki.github.io/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 15:56:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chongniki.github.io/links/</guid>
      <description> github linkedin facebook twiter </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>